they were in high school when they met
and things got kind of awkward
the sparks in the air
he would stare at her and claps
and she would try to act cool
but it was obvious like
oh
they will be together
and one day she said
write me a love song
cause i know you'll make it beautiful
and maybe i'll call you my sweetheart
i promise nobody can steal me away
a and i am your oars
because i want you
and i wanted you to know
he looked at her
and then he smiled
picked up a pen and paper
started writing
probably something about the eyes and how they're always shining
or something completion
oh baby
i only want you
oh
it's true
and then he said
i wrote you a love song
and i tried to make it beautiful
it's a song about you
sweet
it's sweetheart
and how nobody can steal me your way
yeah
i am your horse
cause i want you
and i wanted you to know
as he sang
she started to dance
grabbed his arm and took his hand
he held her close under the moonlight
as they kept on dancing
and now they're singing a love song
and they sing it kind of beautiful
all in each other's way
harvey
i promise nobody can get in their way
or steal the show
oh
they're in love now
and i wanted you to know
hi
let's go
the forecast forecast a lot of sunshine
blue skies were lean clouds
just the perfect day to go check your
it feels like it's better freaking
sorry
don't call me
cause
i'm gonna be on
out you got to do it
feels like it's been a freaking bad game
sorry
don't call me
cause i'm gonna be on the trion
a fresh caroe on a lot of brandy
honey and no matter shots
seven golden hour
like a boss
and they say yo
you got two more
like a poem for fish shop
for you
is he trying to take it higher
only spending and change what you could do this forever
chilling what the heart is gone
they all wanna welcome you to the private penthouse
su
i've got the key
you've got a hell on speed
ocean view from the highest thing
i've come
it's so cold
it feels like it's better freaking back
sorry
don't call me
cause
i'm gonna be on sunny day
make way
all the stressing out you got to do
it feels like
i'll change that
but again you
it's so good
jas and a deli
with my homies or friendly here
we invite only positivity to this part
don't want no drama with that in the vea look
i just wanna let it all go
yeah
i can't say no
and i'm just afraid don't wanna home or gasly
was so nice
only got good vibes
yeah
we hear chilling
chilling
way feels like
all the stressing you out today feels like
game
sorry
don't call because i'm gonna be on grade
sunny day
sunny day dressing down
yeah
not today
it feels like it's better freaking that day
sorry
closer to dance for me
easy tiger
easy
let your hair down come closer
let me see all your million faces and all you million mistakes
you don't need to
closer
so that we can be to
no matter at all we've done
your eyelids in perfect lips got me rushing painting on so
you open the fra in my head
my darling
i got there has been
no matter
no more
leave
all those words
winds cannot touch the soul
if i'm in
stay on track under attack
they burned
and we say more to each other